Claudinéa de Almeida

37 Shanard Road, Santry, Dublin 9, Dublin

Phone: 0858271084 - E-mail: designerclau@gmail.com

Stamp 1G: Available to work full-time.

Summary _____

Responsible for the provision of personal and basic health care to clients, assisting them to gain confidence in the performance of their day to day self-care chores. Outline of a stimulating environment in which the emotional, social, physical, and psychological needs of the individuals are met. Experienced at Home Care and Nursing Home.

HIGHLIGHTS

- Portuguese Native Speaker
- Advanced English speaker
- Teamwork
- Problem-solving
- Multitasking
- High Resilience
- Motivated
- A caring nature
- An approachable nature
- Great communication skills
- Excellent listening skills
- Reliability
- Large organizational skills

Skills

Healthcare Fundamentals,

Work Ethics,

Human Anatomy,

Hygiene and Prophylaxis,

Fluids and nutrition,

Awareness of mental health, dementia and learning disability,

Safeguarding adults and children,

Health and safety,

Infection prevention and control.

Experience_

04/2022 - now – Cowper Care – Gascoigne nursing home

HealthCare Assistant

Treat residents as individuals and respect their preferences and choices as far as possible.

Help residents to achieve independence where possible.

Daily care of residents in the nursing home. It helps them perform basic tasks, including washing, dressing, serving meals and helping to feed patients.

It also monitors their conditions and updating the nurses on the residents' progress.

Following the guidelines of the HSE during the Coronavirus event using PPE and other procedures washing hands, control and infection controls.

07/2021 - 03/2022 - Ann's Home

Home Care Assistant

Daily care of clients in their own home. It helps them perform basic tasks, including washing, dressing, serving meals and helping to feed patients.

It also monitors their conditions and regular reporting to the supervisor or manager.

11/2019 – 07/2021 – FirstCare – Beneavin House

HealthCare Assistant

Treat residents as individuals and respect their preferences and choices as far as possible.

Help residents to achieve independence where possible.

Daily care of residents in the nursing home. It helps them perform basic tasks, including washing, dressing, serving meals and helping to feed patients.

It also monitors their conditions throughout the day such as by taking temperatures and weight, checking skins. I maintain regular contact with nurses and responsible for updating them on the residents' progress.

Following the guidelines of the HSE during the Coronavirus event using PPE such as:

- Social distancing.
- Direct contact with body fluids.
- Present in the same room for more than 15 minutes.
- Residents with total isolation for suspected cases (Full PPE).

2019-2019 - Caremark

Home Care Assistant

Performing basic tasks, including washing, dressing, and eating meals. It also monitors their condition throughout the visit. I maintain regular contact with supervisors and is responsible for updating them on the patient progress.

Education	
Technical Nursing Assistant (Level 6) – Evolution College – Brazil GPA: 95.33 (Certificate Translated)	

Additional Qualifications	

CPR and AED Program – Cowper Care

Dementia Capable Care – Chris Prevention Institute

QQI 5 Care Skills - CPL

Infection Prevention and Control – Firstcare Nursing Home

Manual Handling/Patient Moving – DML Training

Fire Safety Training – Firstcare Nursing Home

Practical Mandatory Training (Manual Handling/Patient Moving) - Caremark

Manual Handling - Rathfarnham Day Care

Fire Safety Training – Rathfarnham Day Care

Children First – HSALanD